<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>MoneyTales</title>
    <language>en-en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 MoneyTales</copyright>
    <itunes:subtitle>Financial literacy for kids with fictional stories</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Financial literacy for kids with fictional stories</itunes:summary>
    <description>Financial literacy for kids with fictional stories</description>
    <webMaster>Super Podcaster</webMaster>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Super Podcaster</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email/>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/MoneyTales.jpg"/>
    <itunes:category text="Education">
      <itunes:category text="Self-Improvement"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    <item>
      <title>Thor and the Golden Apples</title>
      <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Thor and the Golden Apples</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Once upon a time in the magical land of Asgard, Thor, the mighty god of thunder, loved to feast on golden apples. These apples were not just any fruit—they were special because they gave him strength ...</itunes:summary>
      <description>Once upon a time in the magical land of Asgard, Thor, the mighty god of thunder, loved to feast on golden apples. These apples were not just any fruit—they were special because they gave him strength and energy to protect his friends and family. But there was one rule: each apple tree only grew three apples every month.

One sunny morning, Thor woke up with a rumbling tummy. &quot;I could really use a golden apple right now!&quot; he said as he walked to the orchard. When he arrived, he saw three shiny, juicy apples hanging from the tree. His mouth watered just looking at them.

&quot;Wow, these look delicious!&quot; Thor exclaimed. He reached out to grab all three apples. But before he could pluck them, a wise old owl named Odin swooped down and said, &quot;Hold on, young Thor! Do you really need all three apples today?&quot;

Thor scratched his head. &quot;Well, I'm hungry now, so... yes?&quot;

Odin chuckled. &quot;If you eat all three today, what will you eat next week when you're hungry again? Those apples won’t grow back for another whole month.&quot;

Thor paused. He hadn't thought about that. &quot;Hmm,&quot; he said, tapping his chin. &quot;What should I do?&quot;

Odin smiled kindly. &quot;Why not take just one apple today? That way, you’ll have two left for later. You can enjoy this apple now and still have some saved for when you truly need them.&quot;

Thor frowned. &quot;But it’s so hard to wait! These apples are so yummy!&quot;

&quot;I know,&quot; said Odin. &quot;Waiting isn’t always easy, but it makes the reward even sweeter. Imagine how happy you’ll be next week when you’re tired or hungry and you still have an apple waiting for you.&quot;

Thor thought about it for a moment. Then he nodded. &quot;Okay, I’ll try it your way. One apple today and two for later.&quot; Carefully, he picked one golden apple and took a big bite. It tasted amazing!

Over the next few weeks, Thor practiced patience. Whenever he felt like eating more than one apple, he reminded himself how good it would feel to save some for later. And guess what? Every time he waited, he felt proud of himself—and the apples he saved tasted extra delicious!

One day, a big storm hit Asgard. The winds blew fiercely, and everyone needed Thor’s help to keep them safe. After hours of swinging his hammer and battling the storm, Thor was exhausted. But then he remembered—he still had two golden apples left!

He ate one apple, and instantly, his strength returned. With renewed energy, he finished protecting the kingdom and brought peace back to Asgard. Everyone cheered for their brave hero.

Later that evening, Thor sat under the starry sky with Odin. &quot;You know,&quot; Thor said, &quot;waiting wasn’t so bad after all. Saving those apples helped me when I needed them most.&quot;

Odin nodded wisely. &quot;That’s the magic of patience, my friend. Sometimes, waiting a little while makes the reward much bigger and better.&quot;

From that day on, Thor became known not just as the god of thunder, but also as the god of smart choices. And whenever someone in Asgard wanted a treat too soon, they’d remember Thor and his golden apples.

The end.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/Thor_delayed%20gratification_20250411_100609%2FThor_delayed%20gratification.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Thor_delayed gratification_20250411_100609</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 10:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpongeBob Saves the Day</title>
      <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>SpongeBob Saves the Day</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>One sunny morning in Bikini Bottom, SpongeBob SquarePants woke up with a big smile on his face. Today was a special day! The Krusty Krab was introducing a brand-new burger called the &quot;Krabby Deluxe,&quot; ...</itunes:summary>
      <description>One sunny morning in Bikini Bottom, SpongeBob SquarePants woke up with a big smile on his face. Today was a special day! The Krusty Krab was introducing a brand-new burger called the &quot;Krabby Deluxe,&quot; and SpongeBob couldn’t wait to try it. He bounced out of bed, put on his square pants, and headed straight to work.

When SpongeBob arrived at the Krusty Krab, Mr. Krabs greeted him with a twinkle in his eye. &quot;Ahoy, me boy! The Krabby Deluxe is ready, but there's a catch—it costs five shiny gold doubloons!&quot;

SpongeBob’s eyes widened. &quot;Five doubloons? That’s a lot of money!&quot; He only had one doubloon saved up from his last paycheck. 

Mr. Krabs chuckled. &quot;Aye, lad, good things come to those who save. If you want that Krabby Deluxe, you’ll need to save your doubloons bit by bit.&quot;

Determined to taste the delicious new burger, SpongeBob decided to start saving right away. But saving wasn’t as easy as he thought. On his way home, he passed Jellyfish Fields, where Patrick Star was flying kites shaped like jellyfish. &quot;Hey, SpongeBob! Want to buy a kite? Only three doubloons!&quot;

SpongeBob hesitated. The kite looked so fun, and Patrick was his best friend. But then he remembered the Krabby Deluxe. &quot;Sorry, Patrick. I’m saving my doubloons for something extra special.&quot;

Patrick shrugged. &quot;Suit yourself. But don’t forget to have fun too!&quot;

The next day, Squidward invited SpongeBob to an art gallery opening at the Bikini Bottom Museum. &quot;Tickets are just two doubloons,&quot; Squidward said with a smug grin. &quot;You wouldn’t want to miss this masterpiece, would you?&quot;

SpongeBob felt tempted. The paintings did look fancy, but he shook his head. &quot;Thanks, Squidward, but I’ve got my eye on something even better—the Krabby Deluxe!&quot;

Days turned into weeks, and SpongeBob kept putting his doubloons into a little jar he labeled “Krabby Deluxe Fund.” It wasn’t always easy to say no to toys, games, and snacks, but every time he added a doubloon to the jar, he felt proud of himself.

Finally, the big day arrived. SpongeBob counted his doubloons—five shiny gold ones! He ran to the Krusty Krab, heart pounding with excitement. When he handed over his doubloons to Mr. Krabs, he received the Krabby Deluxe in return. It was even more amazing than he imagined: perfectly grilled patties, gooey cheese, crispy lettuce, and a secret sauce that made his taste buds dance.

As SpongeBob took his first bite, Patrick and Squidward walked in. &quot;So, how is it?&quot; Patrick asked.

&quot;It’s the best thing ever!&quot; SpongeBob exclaimed. &quot;And the best part is, I earned it by saving my doubloons.&quot;

Squidward raised an eyebrow. &quot;Saving? That sounds boring.&quot;

But SpongeBob smiled. &quot;It might take time, but saving makes the reward even sweeter—or in this case, tastier!&quot;

From that day on, SpongeBob became the savings champion of Bikini Bottom. He taught Patrick how to save for a new rock to sleep under and helped Squidward save for a clarinet upgrade. Everyone learned that patience and planning could turn small coins into big dreams.

And so, the citizens of Bikini Bottom discovered that saving wasn’t just about doubloons—it was about making wishes come true, one coin at a time.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/SpongeBob%20SquarePants_saving%20money_20250411_032250%2FSpongeBob%20SquarePants_saving%20money.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">SpongeBob SquarePants_saving money_20250411_032250</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:22:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iron Man and the Golden Gadgets</title>
      <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Iron Man and the Golden Gadgets</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>One sunny morning in Stark Tower, Tony Stark was tinkering with his latest invention—a shiny new gadget he called the &quot;Auto-Cleaner 3000.&quot; It was a small robot that could clean up any mess in seconds....</itunes:summary>
      <description>One sunny morning in Stark Tower, Tony Stark was tinkering with his latest invention—a shiny new gadget he called the &quot;Auto-Cleaner 3000.&quot; It was a small robot that could clean up any mess in seconds. Pepper walked into the lab and raised an eyebrow. &quot;Tony, why are you making another gadget? Don't you already have enough robots?&quot;

Tony grinned. &quot;Pepper, there’s always room for one more awesome invention! Besides, this one is special. I’m going to sell it to people so they can keep their homes super clean without lifting a finger.&quot;

Pepper crossed her arms. &quot;That sounds great, but how will you make sure people want to buy it?&quot;

Tony scratched his head. He hadn’t thought about that part yet. Just then, Happy Hogan walked in holding a tray of snacks. &quot;Hey, boss. Did someone say selling stuff? I used to sell lemonade when I was a kid. Let me tell you, it wasn’t as easy as it sounds!&quot;

Tony perked up. &quot;Lemonade? Tell me more, Happy!&quot;

Happy sat down and began sharing his story. &quot;Well, first, I had to figure out what people wanted. Then, I had to work hard to make my lemonade stand look nice and make the best lemonade ever. After all that, I earned money because people liked what I was selling.&quot;

Tony nodded slowly. &quot;So, if I want people to buy my Auto-Cleaner 3000, I need to show them why it’s worth their money.&quot;

&quot;Exactly!&quot; said Happy. &quot;And remember, earning money isn’t just about having a cool idea—it’s about putting in the effort to make it happen.&quot;

Inspired, Tony decided to test his gadget at a local park where families often gathered. He set up a booth with a sign that read, “Try the Amazing Auto-Cleaner 3000!” At first, no one paid attention. But Tony didn’t give up. He started demonstrating how the little robot could pick up crumbs, sweep leaves, and even organize toys. Soon, kids and parents were crowding around, amazed by the clever invention.

A boy named Max asked, &quot;How much does it cost?&quot; Tony smiled and said, &quot;It costs ten coins, but trust me, it’ll save you hours of cleaning time!&quot;

Max looked unsure. &quot;I only have five coins. Can I still get one?&quot;

Tony thought for a moment. &quot;You know what? If you help me spread the word about the Auto-Cleaner 3000, I’ll let you have one for five coins. Deal?&quot;

Max happily agreed and ran off to tell his friends. By the end of the day, Tony had sold dozens of gadgets and earned a pile of coins. More importantly, he learned something valuable: earning money takes creativity, hard work, and understanding what others need.

As Tony flew back to Stark Tower in his Iron Man suit, he felt proud of himself—not just for inventing something cool, but for working hard to share it with the world. From that day on, whenever he created something new, he remembered Happy’s advice: earning money isn’t just about ideas; it’s about effort and making things people truly value.

And guess what? The next weekend, Max came back to Tony’s booth with a jar full of coins. This time, he had saved enough to buy two Auto-Cleaner 3000s—one for himself and one for his little sister. Tony gave him a thumbs-up and said, &quot;Great job, Max! Saving your coins really pays off, doesn’t it?&quot;

The End</description>
      <enclosure url="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/Iron%20Man_earning%20money_20250411_033148%2FIron%20Man_earning%20money.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Iron Man_earning money_20250411_033148</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:31:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Sneaky Online Spell</title>
      <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Harry Potter and the Sneaky Online Spell</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>One sunny afternoon at Hogwarts, Harry Potter was sitting in the Gryffindor common room with his best friends, Hermione Granger and Ron Weasley. They were chatting about their latest adventure when He...</itunes:summary>
      <description>One sunny afternoon at Hogwarts, Harry Potter was sitting in the Gryffindor common room with his best friends, Hermione Granger and Ron Weasley. They were chatting about their latest adventure when Hedwig swooped in with a letter tied to her leg. Harry untied it curiously and read aloud, &quot;Congratulations, Harry! You've won 1,000 Galleons in the Wizarding Web Sweepstakes!&quot;

Ron's eyes widened. &quot;Blimey, Harry! That's enough to buy a lifetime supply of Chocolate Frogs!&quot;

Hermione frowned and crossed her arms. &quot;Wait a minute. Did you even enter a contest, Harry?&quot;

Harry shook his head. &quot;No, I don’t think so.&quot;

&quot;Exactly,&quot; said Hermione. &quot;This sounds fishy. Let’s investigate before we do anything.&quot;

The trio decided to visit Professor McGonagall, who was known for her wisdom and love of cats. When they showed her the letter, she adjusted her glasses and said, &quot;Ah, this is what we call an online scam. Some sneaky wizards or witches try to trick people into giving away their information or money by pretending to offer something amazing.&quot;

&quot;But how does it work?&quot; asked Ron.

Professor McGonagall explained, &quot;Imagine someone sends you a message saying you’ve won a broomstick, but first, you need to send them your vault key to claim it. Once they have your key, they can take all your gold without you realizing it until it's too late.&quot;

Harry gasped. &quot;That’s terrible!&quot;

&quot;It is,&quot; agreed Professor McGonagall. &quot;But there are ways to protect yourself. Always check if the offer is real by asking trusted adults or looking for clues that it might be fake. And never share personal information like passwords or vault keys online.&quot;

Feeling inspired, Harry, Ron, and Hermione decided to spread the word about online scams to their fellow students. They created posters with fun rhymes like:

&quot;If it seems too good to be true,  
A scam might be waiting just for you!  
Ask a teacher, ask a friend,  
Before you click or send.&quot;

Soon, everyone at Hogwarts knew how to spot a scam. Even Peeves the Poltergeist stopped playing tricks on students long enough to listen to Hermione explain why sharing secrets online wasn’t wise.

A few days later, another owl arrived with a new letter for Harry. This time, it was from Gringotts Bank, thanking him for being cautious and rewarding him with a small bag of Galleons for helping educate others about staying safe online.

As they sat by the lake counting the coins, Ron grinned. &quot;See? Being careful pays off—literally!&quot;

Harry nodded. &quot;And now we know: if something feels wrong or too magical to be true, it’s better to double-check than risk losing everything.&quot;

From then on, Harry and his friends became heroes not just for fighting dark wizards but also for teaching everyone the importance of staying smart and safe in the wizarding world—and beyond.

The end.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/Harry%20Potter_online%20scams_20250411_094654%2FHarry%20Potter_online%20scams.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Harry Potter_online scams_20250411_094654</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:46:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Magical Money Plan</title>
      <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Harry Potter and the Magical Money Plan</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>One sunny morning at Hogwarts, Harry Potter woke up with a big smile. Today was special because Hogsmeade weekend was here! He couldn't wait to visit Honeydukes for chocolate frogs and Zonko's for mag...</itunes:summary>
      <description>One sunny morning at Hogwarts, Harry Potter woke up with a big smile. Today was special because Hogsmeade weekend was here! He couldn't wait to visit Honeydukes for chocolate frogs and Zonko's for magical jokes. But as he reached for his money bag, something felt different. It was lighter than usual.

&quot;Uh-oh,&quot; Harry muttered. &quot;I don’t think I have enough gold.&quot;

Ron Weasley yawned and sat up in bed. &quot;What’s wrong, mate?&quot;

&quot;I only have five Galleons left,&quot; said Harry. &quot;And I want to buy so many things today!&quot;

Hermione Granger, who had been reading her book, looked over. &quot;Maybe you should make a plan before we go shopping,&quot; she suggested wisely. &quot;Budgeting is important, even in the wizarding world.&quot;

&quot;A what?&quot; asked Ron, scratching his head.

&quot;A budget,&quot; Hermione explained. &quot;It means deciding how much you’ll spend on each thing ahead of time. That way, you won’t run out of money too quickly.&quot;

Harry thought about it. &quot;Okay, let’s try that. How do I start?&quot;

Hermione pulled out a piece of parchment and started writing. &quot;First, write down everything you want to buy. Then decide how much gold to spend on each item.&quot;

Together, they made a list:
- Chocolate Frogs: 2 Galleons
- Exploding Snap cards: 1 Galleon
- A new quill from Scrivenshaft’s: 1 Galleon
- Something fun but unexpected: 1 Galleon

&quot;That adds up perfectly!&quot; said Hermione, clapping her hands. &quot;Now stick to your plan when we’re in Hogsmeade.&quot;

When they arrived at Hogsmeade, Harry stuck close to his friends. At Honeydukes, the shelves were filled with colorful candies. Harry picked two boxes of Chocolate Frogs just like he planned. Next, they visited Zonko’s Joke Shop, where Ron found some Dungbombs he wanted. Harry laughed but reminded himself not to stray from his budget.

At Scrivenshaft’s Quill Shop, Harry admired all the shiny quills. One caught his eye—it sparkled like stars! Even though it cost more than he expected, he remembered his budget and chose a simpler one instead.

Finally, there was 1 Galleon left for something unexpected. As they strolled past Dervish and Banges, Harry spotted a small jar labeled *Invisibility Potion Sample*. It wasn’t much, but it could be useful someday. He bought it, feeling proud of sticking to his plan.

On the way back to Hogwarts, Ron held up his bag of sweets. &quot;This was such a great day! Thanks for sharing your treats, Harry.&quot;

Harry grinned. &quot;And thanks to Hermione for teaching me about budgets. Now I didn’t waste my gold, and I still got everything I needed—and even something extra!&quot;

Hermione smiled. &quot;See? Budgeting isn’t boring; it’s actually kind of magical. You can enjoy yourself without worrying about running out of money.&quot;

From then on, whenever Harry received gold, he always made a plan first. Whether it was saving for Christmas presents or planning another trip to Hogsmeade, he learned that being careful with his coins helped him make smarter choices.

And so, Harry discovered that just like spells, a good budget could work wonders too.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/Harry%20Potter_budgeting_20250412_131313%2FHarry%20Potter_budgeting.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Harry Potter_budgeting_20250412_131313</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 13:13:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batman's Big Decision</title>
      <itunes:author>Super Podcaster</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Batman's Big Decision</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>One sunny morning in Gotham City, Batman was sitting in the Batcave thinking about his next big purchase. He had saved up a lot of money from his adventures helping people and catching bad guys. On hi...</itunes:summary>
      <description>One sunny morning in Gotham City, Batman was sitting in the Batcave thinking about his next big purchase. He had saved up a lot of money from his adventures helping people and catching bad guys. On his desk were two shiny catalogs. One was filled with pictures of cool new gadgets like laser gloves and smoke-blasting boots. The other catalog showed sturdy but plain tools like ropes, flashlights, and first-aid kits.

&quot;Wow,&quot; Batman said to himself, &quot;I could get so many awesome things from this gadget catalog! Imagine how cool I’d look flying around with jet-powered wings!&quot;

Just then, Robin burst into the Batcave holding a tray of cookies. &quot;Hey, Batman! What are you looking at?&quot;

&quot;I’m trying to decide what to buy with my savings,&quot; Batman replied. &quot;But I can’t figure out which is better—cool stuff or boring stuff.&quot;

Robin peeked at the catalogs. &quot;Cool stuff wins every time, right? Who wouldn’t want laser gloves?&quot;

Batman chuckled. &quot;Well, let’s think about it. Remember last week when we were chasing the Joker through that dark tunnel? What did we need most then?&quot;

Robin thought for a moment. &quot;Uh…flashlights?&quot;

&quot;Exactly!&quot; Batman said, pointing at the second catalog. &quot;A flashlight isn’t as exciting as laser gloves, but it helps us see where we’re going. That’s something we *need*. Laser gloves might be fun, but they aren’t as useful in every situation.&quot;

Robin nodded slowly. &quot;So…needs are things we really have to have, and wants are just extra stuff we like?&quot;

&quot;You’ve got it!&quot; Batman grinned. &quot;Now, here’s another example. If our Batmobile breaks down, do we need a brand-new one with turbo boosters and neon lights, or will fixing the old one work just fine?&quot;

Robin scratched his head. &quot;Fixing the old one is probably cheaper, huh?&quot;

&quot;Right again,&quot; Batman said. &quot;Sometimes, spending money on what we *want* means we don’t have enough left for what we *need*. And being a superhero means always being ready to help others, even if it’s not flashy.&quot;

Suddenly, the Bat-Signal lit up the sky outside. Commissioner Gordon needed them right away! Batman grabbed his utility belt and ran toward the Batmobile, with Robin close behind.

When they arrived at the scene, they found Penguin blocking the streets with an enormous ice machine, freezing everything in sight. Batman quickly pulled out his trusty rope and flashlight—the same ones he’d been considering earlier—and swung into action. Within minutes, he stopped the chaos and saved the day.

Back in the Batcave later that night, Batman looked at the catalogs again. This time, he circled a few items in the practical catalog and closed the gadget one.

&quot;You know, Robin,&quot; he said, &quot;it feels good to make smart choices. I’ll still save some money for fun things, but knowing I’m prepared to help Gotham makes me feel like the best version of myself.&quot;

Robin smiled. &quot;Yeah, Batman. You don’t need fancy gadgets to be a hero—you already are one!&quot;

And from that day on, Batman made sure to balance his needs and wants, proving that even superheroes have to make wise decisions. 

The end.</description>
      <enclosure url="https://money-tales-pod.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/Batman_needs%20vs%20wants_20250411_033148%2FBatman_needs%20vs%20wants.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">Batman_needs vs wants_20250411_033148</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:31:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
